♪ Wah ooh ♪
- [Tom] "Happy Days" is
filmed before a live audience.
- Yes, ladies and gentlemen, tonight,
live from Arnold's Drive-In
and Milwaukee Fried Chicken Stand,
You Wanted to See It brings you
one of the most exciting events
it's ever been our privilege to bring you.
(audience cheering)
- Okay, kids, Arnold's is proud to present
Kenosha, Wisconsin's own Weezer!
(crowd cheering)
- Oh, hey, hey, please try the fish.
(audience laughing)
- And a one, and a two,
and a three, and a four.
♪ What's with these
homies dissin' my girl ♪
♪ Why do they gotta front ♪
♪ What did we ever do to these guys ♪
♪ That made them so violent ♪
♪ Woo hoo, but you know I'm yours ♪
♪ Woo hoo, and I know you're mine ♪
♪ Woo hoo, and that's for all time ♪
♪ Woo-ee-ooh, I look
just like Buddy Holly ♪
♪ Oh, oh, and you're Mary Tyler Moore ♪
♪ I don't care what they
say about us anyway ♪
♪ I don't care about that ♪
(rock guitar music)
♪ Don't you ever fear, I'm always near ♪
♪ I know that you need help ♪
♪ Your tongue is twisted,
your eyes are slit ♪
♪ You need a guardian ♪
♪ Woo hoo, and you know I'm yours ♪
♪ Woo hoo, and I know you're mine ♪
♪ Woo hoo, and that's for all time ♪
♪ Woo-ee-ooh, I look
just like Buddy Holly ♪
♪ Oh, oh, and you're Mary Tyler Moore ♪
♪ I don't care what they
say about us anyway ♪
♪ I don't care 'bout that ♪
(audience groaning)
- [Richie] Stay tuned
for more "Happy Days."
♪ Bang, bang, knock on the door ♪
♪ Another big bang,
get down on the floor ♪
♪ Oh no, what do we do ♪
♪ Don't look now but I lost my shoe ♪
♪ I can't run and I can't kick ♪
♪ What's a matter, babe,
are you feelin' sick ♪
♪ What's a matter, what's a
matter, what's a matter you ♪
♪ What's a matter, babe,
are you feelin' blue ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
(rock guitar music)
♪ And that's for all time ♪
♪ Woo-ee-oo, I look
just like Buddy Holly ♪
♪ Oh, oh, and you're Mary Tyler Moore ♪
♪ I don't care what they
say about us anyway ♪
♪ I don't care 'bout that ♪
(crowd cheering)
- [Girl] Fonzarelli!
- Good work, guys.
I mean you were really great.
- [Man] Thanks, Al.
- Sensational.
Hey, anyone try the fish tonight?
- It's not so good, Al.
- Not so good, Al.
Yeah, yeah, yep, yep, yep.
(audience laughing)